我认为这就在那里
Okay.Right about there. I think that's it.
真不敢相信我们竟然买了这玩意
l can't believe we actually bought this thing.
所以说慈善拍卖能举行开幕酒会是有原因的
There's a reason charity auctions have an open bar.
你不觉得… 这画有点让人觉得毛骨悚然吗？
Don't you think, I don't know, it's kind of creepy?
没事的 我来保障你的安全
It's okay. I'll keep you safe.
或许你才是那个我应该觉得害怕的人
Maybe you're the one I ought to be scared of?
- 我们上楼去吧 - 给我10分钟来锁门
- Let's go upstairs. - Give me two minutes to lock up.
给我1分钟好了
Make that one minute.
你要是不快点的话 我就自己先开始了
If you don't hurry up.I'm gonna start without you.
亲爱的 开下灯 我看不清
Babe, get the lights.I can't see a thing.
你有闻到什么味道吗？
You spill something?
安？
Ann?
Ann!
《邪恶力量》
7 4 2 0
Seven, four, two, zero.
好的 已经存进去了 太好了
All right, you're in there. Perfect.
你的名字是以「Y」结尾还是以「I」结尾的Brandy？
Is "Brandy" with a Y or an I?
好了 我得走了 别走开 我等下就回来
All right, listen, I gotta go. Hold that.thought. l'll be right back, okay?
- 我想我查到了一些什么 - 我也是
- All right. So I think I got something. - Yeah, me too.
我觉得我们该歇会了 就一会儿
I think we need to take.a little shore leave, just a little bit.
你觉得怎样？我和那边那个正打得火热
What do you think, huh?I'm so in the door with this one.
那我们今天是什么身份 迪恩？摇滚明星吗？
So, what are we today, Dean? Are we rock stars?
还是什么特种部队？
Are we Army Rangers?
我们是L。-A的星探 来找有特殊才艺的人
Reality-TV scouts looking for people.with special skills.
还不是那么离谱 对吧？
I mean, hey, it's notthat far off, right?
顺便说句 她还有个朋友也在那边
By the way.She's got a friend over there.
我可以介绍你们认识 你觉得怎样？
Probably hook you up. What do you think?
迪恩 还是不必了 我可以自己去找约会
No, thanks. I can get my own dates.
对 你是可以 可是你根本没去找
Yeah, you can, but you don't.
- 你这话什么意思？- 没什么意思 你查到什么？
- What is that supposed to mean? - Nothing. What do you got?
几天前纽约纽柏兹的马克和安·特莱斯卡夫妇
Mark and Ann Telesca of New Paltz, New York…
被发现陈尸家中
were both found dead in their home.
前几天
a few days ago.
喉咙被切开 现场没有任何指纹
Throats were slit. There were no prints.
没发现凶器 所有的 迪恩？
no murder weapons, all-Dean.
没发现指纹和凶器 所有的门窗都从里面上锁
No prints, no murder weapons, all doors and windows locked from the inside.
可能只是普通的谋杀案而已 你知道 不是我们该管的事
Could just be a garden-variety murder, not our department.
- 不 爸爸可不那么觉得 - 什么意思？
- No. Dad says different. - What do you mean?
看 爸爸有注意到发生在
Look. Dad noted three murders.
纽约郊区同一地带的三起谋杀案
in the same area of upstate New York.
第一起在这 1912年 第二起是1945年
First one right here, 1912, the second one in 1945…
第三起是1970年 和特莱斯卡夫妇一样的状况
and the third in 1970, the same m.o. as the Telescas.
喉咙被切开 房子都从里面上锁
The throats were slit, the houses were locked from the inside.
几起谋杀案之间隔了那么久
Time passed between the murders.
可能除了爸爸之外没人注意到这种相似性
Nobody tracked the pattern but Dad.
他一直在注意看有没其他相似的案子
He kept his eyes peeled for another one.
- 我们现在找到一个了- 正是
- And now we got one? - Exactly.
我同意 这事值得去看下
All right, l'm with you.It's worth checking out.
可是总不能现在就启程去 对吧？
We can't pick this up till first thing, though, right?
- 对- 那好
- Yeah. - Good.
- 女士们 有没想我啊？- 迪恩…
- Dean. - Ladies. Did you miss me?
- 玩笑而已 - 我只是一个小孩
- Hell, yeah. - l'm just kid-
我和制片人谈过了 事情进展的很顺利
Listen, I talked to my producer, and it is looking good.
酷极了
Great.Cool.
噢 这一点都不好笑
Man, that's so not cool.
我用EMF把特莱斯卡的房子扫视过一遍 没什么发现
I just swept the Telesca house with the EMF. It's clean.
- 而昨天晚上当你… 出去… - 噢 很尽兴
- And last night, while you were out… - Good times.
我查过了这所房子的历史记录
l checked the history of the house.
没有灵异事件 没有暴力犯罪
No hauntings, no violent crimes.
关于特莱斯卡一家也没什么奇怪的事情
Nothing strange about the Telescas.
那么要是不是人和房子的问题的话
So if it's not the people, and it's not the house…
或许是里面的摆设 带有诅咒的物品或是什么
then, uh, maybe it's the contents, a cursed object.
- 房子没有问题 - 你说过了
- House is clean. - Yeah, I know, you said that.
不 我是说里面已经空了 什么家具也没有
No, I mean it's empty.No furniture or nothing.
那所有的东西都哪去了？
Where's all their stuff?
默拍 财产出售
Consignment auctions, estate sales.
这看起来就象是专门为W。-A。-S。-P。-S举行的旧物出售
Looks like a garage sale for Wasps.
要是你问我的话
If you ask me.
有什么能效劳的吗？
Can I help you gentlemen?
我能来杯香槟吗？
I'd like some champagne, please.
他不是侍应生
He's not a waiter.
我是萨姆·康纳斯
I'm Sam Connors.
这位是我大哥迪恩
That's my brother, Dean.
我们是来自Connors Limited的艺术经销商
We are art dealers, with Connors Limited.
- 你们是艺术经销商？- 没错
- You're art dealers? - That's right.
我是丹尼尔·布莱克 这里是我开的拍卖行
I'm Daniel Blake.This is my auction house.
今天是个私人的展览
Now, gentlemen, this is a private showing…
我记得贵宾名单上没有你们的名字
and I don't remember seeing you on the guest list.
我们名字在上面 你去再看下就可以了
We're there, Chuckles, just need to take another look.
噢 终于来了
Oh. Finally. Hmm.
干杯
Cheers.
美国原始派艺术的代表作 你们觉得呢？
A fine example of American primitive, wouldn't you say?
我觉得比起摩西奶奶 更象是格兰特·伍德的作品
Well, l'd say it's more Grant Wood than Grandma Moses.
你已经知道了 你只是在试探我知不知道
But you knew that.You just wanted to see if I did.
真是惭愧 开个玩笑 我道歉 我是莎拉·布莱克
Guilty. And clumsy. I apologize.I'm Sarah Blake.
我是萨姆 这是我大哥迪恩
I'm Sam. This is my brother, Dean.
迪恩 要不要再多给你拿点小曲奇饼？
Dean. Can we get you some more mini-quiche?
- 不用了 谢谢 - 有什么能效劳的吗？
- Mm-mm. I'm good. Thanks. - So can I help you with something?
实际上有 能不能和我们说下特莱斯卡的财产的事情？
Yeah, actually. Um, what can you tell us about the Telesca estate?
要是你问我的话 我觉得这么快就
The whole thing's pretty grisly, if you ask me…
卖掉他们的东西实在不敬 可是我父亲有句话说的没错
selling their things this soon, but Dad's right about one thing.
这种煽情主义才会带来大量的客人 甚至是很有钱的客人
Sensationalism brings out the crowds.Even the rich ones.
能不能让我们看下这些东西的出处？
ls it possible to see the provenances?
我想可能不行
l'm afraid there isn't any chance of that.
- 为什么？- 你们并没有在贵宾名单上…
- Why not? - You're not on the guest list.
你们该离开了
I think it's time to leave.
- 我们没必要被两次告诫 - 很显然 你们就是要这样
- Well, we don't have to be told twice. - Apparently, you do.
那好 就这样 我们可不想惹麻烦 我们就走
Okay. It's all right.We don't want any trouble. We'll go.
爸爸 那样真粗鲁
Dad, that was rude.
什么玩意？艺术历史课
Grant Wood Grandma Moses?Art history course.
- 那课很好认识女孩子 - 好象我从不认识你一样
- It's good for meeting girls. - It's like I don't even know you.
那「Providence」是什么意思？
Now, what was the providence?
是一种出处的证明书 就象传记一样 懂吧？
It's a certificate of origin, like a biography.
我们可以用它们来追溯物品的历史
We can use them to track the pieces'history.
看是不是有什么不寻常的过去
See if any has got a freaky past.
我们从那老家伙口中可套不出什么来 可是莎拉… 对
Well, we're not getting anything out of Chuckles, but, uh, Sarah…
也许你可以叫她写在你的餐巾上
Maybe you can get her to write it all on a cocktail napkin.
不是我去
Not me.
不 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
- 钓女孩子是你的专长 迪恩 - 她当时看的可不是我
- Pickups are your thing, Dean. - lt wasn't my butt she was checking out.
所以你是叫我利用她来套话
In other words, you want me to use her to get information.
有时候为了大局是要牺牲下 打给她吧
Sometimes you gotta take one for the team. Call her.
- 地方不错 - 对
- Nice place. - Yeah.
- 很高兴你打给我 虽然很讶异不过还是很高兴 - 真的吗？
- Glad you called. Surprised, but glad. - Yeah?
不过听上去你好象想了很久
Although you seemed to have a hard time getting out the words:
才挤出「你愿意和我共进晚餐？」几个字来
"Would you like to have dinner?"
没错 我已经很久没约过人了
Yeah. I haven't really been on a date in a while.
- 我也一样 - 你开玩笑吧？
- Welcome to the club. - You're kidding me.
- 好了 - 谢谢
Here we are. - Thanks.
酒单
The wine list.
我不知道我们的男主角要什么不过我点一杯啤酒
I don't know about Romeo here, but I'll have a beer.
你呢？
And you?
我也是 好的
Make that two.Certainly.
- 所以你上学时学的是艺术对吧？- 没错 我是个艺术家
- So you studied art in school, huh?It's true. I was an artist.
一个很糟糕的艺术家
A terrible, terrible artist.
- 所以现在才会从事拍卖业 你在读法律预科？- 对
- That's why I'm in the auction business.And you were pre-law? - Yeah.
可是你并没去上法学院 为什么？
But you didn't go to law school.How come?
说来话长
Ah, it's a really long story for another time.
你和我以前遇见过的艺术经销商不同
You're not like any art dealer I've ever met.
你说你也很长一段时间没约会了 是什么意思？
So, what did you mean when you said you hadn't been on a date in a while?
- 想让我觉得我并不是很逊色？- 那句话有很多意思 萨姆
- Making me feel like l'm not a loser? - l'm sure you're many things.
我能确定「逊色」并不是其中之一
I'm also sure loser isn't one of them.
是因为我的母亲 她大概一年前去世了
It was my mom.She died about a year ago.
毫无预警
Totally unexpected.
让我伤心欲绝
It really threw me.
我把自己封闭起来 封闭在一个温暖安全的环境里
I went into this shell.A nice, warm, safe shell.
可是后来 我想了很久… 这并不是她希望看到的结果
But lately l've been thinking, it's not what she would have wanted for me.
所以…
So…
那你呢？你算是个很有魅力的男人
So, what about you?You're a reasonably attractive guy.
- 算是 - 你为什么不去约会？
- Reasonably. - Why haven't you been out and about?
又是说来话长
Another long story for another time.
所以她只是爽快的把「Providences」给你了？
So she just handed the providences over to you, huh?
是Provenances - Provenances
- Provenances. - Provenances?
对 我们回到她的住处 拿了一份文件的复印件
And, yes, we went back to her place, I got a copy of the papers…
- 然后呢？- 没了 就这样 我就走了
- And? - And nothing. That's it. I left.
你没必要只是骗骗她 你可以做点其他特殊的事情？
You didn't have to con her or do any special favors or anything like that?
你能不能不要整天想那些龌龊的事情？
Dean, would you get your mind out of the gutter?
等事情完结之后 我们可以在这地方稍微滞留一会
When this thing's done, we could stick around.
- 为什么？- 方便你再叫她出去
- Why? - So you could take her out again.
很显然你对她有感觉 我都能看得出来
It's obvious you're into her. I see that.
嘿 我找到点资料了
Hey, I think I got something here.
「以赛亚商人一家的肖像画 绘于1910年」
"Portrait of Isaiah Merchant's family, painted 1910."
把买主和爸爸日记上的名字对比下
Now, compare the names of the owners with Dad's journal.
「1912年由彼得·西姆斯第一次购得」
"First purchased in 1912 to Peter Simms."
彼得·西姆斯于1912年被杀
"Peter Simms murdered in 1912."
同样的事情发生在1945年 还有1970年
Same thing in 1945.Oh, same thing in 1970.
然后画就被存起来了
Then stored.
直到上个月才被捐献给一个慈善拍卖会
until it was donated to a charity auction last month…
在那里特莱斯卡买下了这副画
where the Telescas bought it.
所以你觉得是什么？被鬼魂附上了还是被诅咒了？
So, what do you think, it's haunted or cursed?
不管是什么 问题肯定出在画身上
Either way, it's toast.
跟上
Come on.
继续
Go ahead.
丑陋的东西
Ugly-ass thing.
要是你问我的话 我们在帮艺术世界清除异类
If you ask me, we're doing the art world a favor.
- 糟糕 我找不到我钱包了 - 没什么问题吧？
- We got a problem. I can't find my wallet. - How is that my problem?
我想我昨晚掉在拍卖行了
Because I think I dropped it in the warehouse last night.
你在开玩笑对吧？
You're kidding, right?
上面有我的指纹 我的身份证 虽然是我的假身份证
No. I mean, it's got my prints, my ID-Well, my fake lD,
可是不管怎样
But no matter how.
我们还是要得在别人找到前 把钱包找回来 走
But we gotta get it before somebody else finds it. Come on.
你钱包怎么会丢 迪恩？
How do you lose your wallet, Dean?
- 嘿 - 莎拉 嘿
- Hey, guys. - Sarah. Hey.
你们在这干吗？
What are you doing here?
哦…
Oh.
我们 我们要走了 所以过来道别的。-
We-We are leaving town. And, you know, we came to say goodbye.
你在说什么 萨姆？
Oh, what are you talking about, Sam?
我们至少还得待个一两天
We're sticking around for at least another day or two.
萨姆 正好 我还得还你之前欠你的20美元
Sam, by the way, l'm gonna go ahead and give you that 20 bucks I owe you.
我老忘记
I always forget, you know.
给你
There you go.
那我就不陪你们小俩口了 我得去… 那儿…
Well, l'll leave you two crazy kids alone.I gotta go do something.
做点什么
somewhere.
- 那么… - 我昨晚过得很愉快
- So. - I had a good time last night.
- 没错 我也是 - 也许有时间可以再一起出去？
- Yeah. Yeah, I did too. - Maybe we should do it again sometime.
我很乐意 真的 可是迪恩 刚刚只是在胡说而已
You know, I'd love to, I really would, but Dean, he was just screwing around.
- 我们今天真的得走了 - 噢
- We really are taking off today. - Oh. Oh.
- 这太糟了 - 天啊
- Oh, that's too bad. - Oh, my God.
- 什么？- 那
- What? - The.
那幅画… 看起来真不错
That painting looks so good.
如果你是说它有另类的美的话 那可能你说得没错
If you can call that monstrosity good, then, yeah, I guess.
莎拉 那幅画你知道些什么？
Sarah.What do you know about that painting?
不太了解 只是觉得它给我毛骨悚然的感觉
Not much, just that it creeps me out.
我们那天在慈善拍卖上卖给了特莱斯卡夫妇
We sold it to the Telescas at a charity auction the night.
后来他们就被杀了
they were murdered.
所以现在你们打算再次出售吗？
Now you're just gonna sell it again?
我父亲是有这个打算 不过我会阻止他的
As much as my dad wants to, no, I won't let him.
- 我觉得这幅画不怎么样 - 那太好了 千万别卖
- I think it'd be in bad taste. - Good. Yeah.
答应我千万不要卖了 好吗？
You know what?Make sure you don't, okay?
为什么？别告诉我你对那画有兴趣
Why? Don't tell me you're interested in that.
当然不是 才不可能会想买 我得走了 我还有事要办
No. No. God, no. Not in buying it, no.You know what? I gotta go.
我会再找你的 我再打给你
I gotta take care of something.But I will call you back. I will call you.
- 待会见 - 等会 所以你今晚不离开了？
- l'll see you later. - Wait, so you're not leaving tonight?
我想是的 稍后再联络
No, I guess not. l'll see you.
好的
Okay.
我真搞不懂 迪恩 我们明明把那鬼玩意给烧了
I don't understand, Dean.We burned the damn thing.
真是谢谢了 自以为是的家伙
Yeah, thank you, Captain Obvious.
好了 我们得另外找方法来对付它
All right, we just need to figure out another way to get rid of it.
有什么想法吗？
Any ideas?
那好 几乎所有的被鬼附上的油画的传说中
Okay, all right. Well, um, in almost all the lore about haunted paintings…
往往是画中的主题附上了油画
it's always the painting's subject that haunts them.
对吧？所以我们得设法搞清楚那幅鬼画
Yeah? We need to figure out everything there is to know…
画的鬼家庭的所有事情
about that creepy-ass family in that creepy-ass painting.
他们叫什么名字来着？
What were their names again?
- 以赛亚商人一家 对吧？- 没错
- You said the lsaiah Merchant family? - Yeah, that's right.
我查了所有的当地历史宗卷
I dug up every scrap of local history I could find.
- 所以你们是什么犯罪爱好者对吧？- 差不多
- So, uh, are you boys crime buffs? - Kind of.
- 为什么这么问？- 看…
- Yeah. Why do you ask? - Well…
- 没错 这样就说的通了 - 全家都被杀死了吗？
- Yes. Yeah, that sounds about right. - The whole family was killed?
似乎是以赛亚先割破了所有孩子的喉咙
It seems this Isaiah, he slits his kids' throats…
然后是他妻子 最后是他自己
then his wife, then himself.
他是个理发师 用的是把直剃须刀
Now, he was a barber by trade.Used a straight razor.
- 他为什么这么做？- 我们一起来看吧
- Why did he do it? - Well, let's look.
「认识他的人都形容以赛亚 脾气易暴易躁
"People who knew him described Isaiah as having stern and harsh temperament.
对自己的家人也喜欢动用暴力「 对他的妻子
Controlled his family with an iron fist.Wife.
两个儿子和一个收养的女儿
two sons, a dopted daughter."
当时有传言说他妻子打算带着孩子离开他
There were whispers that the wife was gonna take the kids and leave-
在当时的那个年代想想也是理所当然的事情…
Uh, which, of course, you know, in that day and age…
所以老以赛亚索性给他们全体来了次割喉
Um, so instead, old man Isaiah, well, he gave them all a shave.
- 上面有没提及尸体后来怎样了？- 全都被火化了
- Say what happened to the bodies? - Just that they were all cremated.
- 还有别的吗？- 有
- Anything else? - Yeah.
我找到了一张他们全家的合照 就在这本书的某个地方
Actually, I found a picture of the family.It's right here, somewhere.
找到了
Right. Here it is.
- 我们能不能复印一份？- 当然
- Could we get a copy of this, please? - Hmm. Sure.
爸爸… 你答应过我不卖这幅画的
Dad, you promised you wouldn't sell that painting.
我记得 亲爱的 可是伊夫林开出了一个可观的价钱
I know, sweetie, but Evelyn's offered a persuasive amount of money.
这样做真应该感到羞愧
You're shameless, you know that?
为了那笔可观的钱 我宁愿被那么说
For that kind of money, I can afford to be.
听着 我很确定
I'm telling you, man, l'm sure of it.
拍卖行的画像里 画中的父亲是向下看
Painting at the auction house, Dad is looking down.
这张画里 父亲是向外看 画像改变了 迪恩
Painting here, Dad's looking out.The painting has changed, Dean.
所以你觉得父亲被困在这幅画里面了
You think Daddy Dearest is in the painting and handing out…
然后他再象对待他家人一样 对待买这幅画的人？
Columbian neckties like with his family?
没错 看起来事情就是这样
Yeah, it seems like it.
可是要是连他的尸骨都被火化了的话
But if his bones are already dusted.
我们该怎么阻止他？
how are we gonna stop him?
要是画中Isaiah的位置都改变了的话
If lsaiah's position changed.
或许画中其他什么地方也改变了
then maybe other things in the painting changed.
也许从中可以找到什么线索
You know, it could give us some clues.
象是「达芬奇密码」之类的吗？
What, like a Da Vinci Code deal?
我也不清楚 我都还在等那部电影上映
I don't know. l'm just still waiting for the movie on that one.
不管怎样 我们得回去再看下那幅画
Anyway, we gotta get back in and see that painting.
不过这样也好 因为你就有更多时间和你女朋友相处了
Which is good. You can get more time to crush on your girlfriend.
- 哥们… 够了 - 什么？
- Dude, enough already. - What?
什么？自从我们到这地方之后
What? Ever since we got here.
你都一直在试着撮合我和莎拉
you've been trying to pimp me out to Sarah.
- 别管这事了好吧？- 可是你喜欢她 对吧？
- Just back off, all right? - Well, you like her, don't you?
你喜欢她 她也喜欢你 你们都是成年人了
You like her, she likes you, you're consenting adults.
你想说什么 迪恩？
What's the point, Dean?
我们会离开的 我们总会离开的
We'll just leave. We always leave.
我又不是要让你和她结婚
Saml'm not talking about marriage.
我真搞不懂 你为什么那么关心我的感情生活？
I don't get it. What do you care if I hook up?
或许你就不会一直那么暗自神伤了
Because then maybe you wouldn't be so cranky all the time.
说真的 萨姆 这不是只是你交不交女朋友的问题
You know, seriously, Sam, this isn't about just hooking up, okay?
我觉得这个叫莎拉的女孩会对你有帮助的
I mean, I think that this Sarah girl could be good for you.
我并不是有什么不敬的意思
And I don't mean any disrespect.
可是 我肯定所有的一切都是因为杰西卡 对吧？
but I'm sure that this is about Jessica, right?
虽然我不能了解你失去挚爱是什么感觉…
Now, I don't know what it's like to lose somebody like that…
可是… 我知道她也希望你能重新开心起来
but I would think that she would want you to be happy.
上帝也允许我们有时尽情享乐一下 对吧？
God forbid, have fun once in a while.Wouldn't she?
没错 我知道她也是那么希望的
Yeah, I know she would.
你说的没错 有部分原因是因为杰西卡
Yeah, you're right, part of this is about Jessica.
- 可是也不是全部 - 那是什么？
- But not the main part. - What's it about?
算了
Yeah, all right.
我们还是得去看那幅画
We still gotta see that painting.
所以你还是得打电话给莎拉
which means you still gotta call Sarah, so…
莎拉 嘿 我是萨姆 嘿
Sarah, hey, it's Sam. Hey. Hi.
很好 很好 你怎么样？
Good. Good, yeah.Um, what about you?
- 很好 真的很好 - 真流利啊
- Yeah, good. Good, really good. - Smooth.
听着 我和我大哥想
So, uh… So listen, me and my brother were, uh, thinking…
回你那去 再看看那幅画
that maybe we'd like to come back in and look at the painting again.
我想我们可能想买下它
I think maybe we are interested in buying it.
你说什么？你们卖给谁了？
Wait. What? Who'd you sell it to?
莎拉 现在给我她的地址
Sarah, I need an address right now.
- 萨姆 发生什么事了？- 我说过你没必要来的
- Sam, what's happening? - I told you you shouldn't have come.
- 哈罗 有人在家吗？ - 你说伊芙琳可能有危险
- Hello. Anybody home? - You said Evelyn might be in danger.
- 什么危险？- 打不开门
- What kind of danger? - I can't knock this down.
我要撬开了
I gotta pick it.
你们到底是什么人 夜盗吗？
What are you guys, burglars?
我也希望事情就这么简单 听着 你应该呆在车上
l wish it's that simple.You should wait in the car.
- 别出来 - 我当然不会 伊芙琳是我朋友
- It's for your own good. - The hell I will. Evelyn's a friend.
伊芙琳？
Evelyn.
伊芙琳
Evelyn?
伊芙琳？我是莎拉·布莱克
Evelyn? It's Sarah Blake.
- 你没事吧？- 莎拉 别看
- Are you all right? - Sarah, don't. Sarah.
天啊 我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
嘿 你没事吧？
Hey. You all right?
当然有事
No, actually.
我刚刚才向警察撒完谎说是我一个人冲进伊芙琳的家里
l just lied to the cops and told them I went to Evelyn's…
发现她变成那样子的
alone and found her like that.
多谢
Thank you.
不要谢我 要是你们不告诉我到底发生什么事了的话
Don't. l'm about to call them…
我马上打电话叫警察回来
if you don't tell me what the hell's going on.
到底是谁杀死了这些人？
Who's killing these people?
- 「什么」- 什么？
- "What."-What?
不是 「谁」 是要问 「什么」杀死了这些人
It's not "who."It's "what" is killing those people?
莎拉 你看到那幅画动了
Sarah, you saw that painting move.
- 才没有 - 我是看到了
No. No, I was-l was seeing things.
- 不过那是不可能的 - 欢迎来到我们的世界
- It's impossible. - Yeah, well, welcome to our world.
莎拉 我知道这听起来很疯狂…
Sarah, I know this sounds crazy…
可是我们认为那幅画闹鬼
but we think that that painting is haunted.
你在开玩笑对吧？
You're joking.
你是说真的
You're not joking.
- 天啊 这就是我出去约会的对象 - 莎拉 你仔细想想
- God. The guys I go out with. - Sarah, think about it.
伊夫林 特莱斯卡夫妇 他们都买下了那幅画
Evelyn, the Telescas, they both had the painting.
之前也有这样的事情发生 只要这幅画走到什么地方
And there have been others.Wherever this thing goes.
就会有人死亡
people die.
我们正在努力阻止这事情再发生…
And we're just trying to stop it.
这就是事情的真相
And that's the truth.
那你最好能证明给我看 我和你一起走
Well, then I guess you better show me. l'm coming with you.
什么？不行 莎拉 绝对不行 你最好还是先回家去
What? No. Sarah, no.You should just go home.
事情会变得很危险的 而且…
This stuff can get dangerous and…
而且我不想让你受到伤害
And I don't want you to get hurt.
听着 你们可能只是疯子而已
Look, you guys are probably crazy.
可是要是你们说的是实话的话
but if you're right?
我和我父亲卖掉那幅画的时候
Well, me and my dad sold that painting.
我们就可能做了他们被杀的帮凶
We might've got these people killed.
我不是说我不害怕 因为我知道我现在怕得要死
I'm not saying l'm not scared, because I am scared…
可是我也不会选择就此逃避
but l'm not gonna run and hide either.
所以说我们一起去还是怎样？
So are we going or what?
萨姆…
Sam.
娶她吧
Marry that girl.
这里现在不是犯罪现场吗？
Uh, isn't this a crime scene?
你都已经向警察撒谎了 还怕什么？
Well, you already lied to the cops.What's another infraction?
你不怕这画现在就会杀人吗？
Aren't you worried that it's gonna, you know, kill us?
不会 好象晚上才会发生
No. It seems to do its thing at night.
白天我们是安全的
I think we're all right in the daylight.
萨姆 看看这
Sam, check it out.
那把剃刀… 这张照片里是合上的 那幅画上却是打开的
The razor, it's… Uh, It's closed. But it's open in that one.
- 你们在找什么？- 要是那鬼怪改变了画中的内容的话
What? - lf the spirit's changing aspects…
也许它那样做是有原因的
of the painting, maybe it's doing so for a reason.
嘿 看这 画里做背景的那幅画
Hey, hey. Look at this.The painting in the painting.
看起来象一个地下室或陵墓之类的东西
Looks like a crypt or a mausoleum or something.
「默钱特」
"Merchant."
这是找过的第三个墓地了
This is the third boneyard we've checked.
这鬼把我们耍得团团转
I think this ghost is jerking us around.
你们就靠这谋生吗？
So this is what you guys do for a living?
确切来说不算 我们没酬劳可拿
Not exactly. We don't get paid.
祝你好运
Well, mazel tov.
在那边
Over there.
这是我这辈子看过的最可怕的东西
Okay. That, right there, is the creepiest thing I've ever seen.
这是当时的一种传统
It was, uh, sort of a tradition at the time.
有孩子夭折的时候 有时候他们会把那孩子最爱的玩具
Whenever a child died, sometimes they'd preserve the kid's…
放在玻璃箱里 放在墓冢里骨灰罐的旁边
favorite toy in a glass case.Put it next to the headstone or crypt.
- 有发现什么奇怪的事情吗？- 我该从哪开始呢？
- You notice anything strange here? - Uh, where do I start?
我不是这个意思 看看这些骨灰罐
No, that's not what I mean.Look at the urns.
只有四个母亲和三个孩子的
Yeah, there are only four. Yeah, mom and the three kids.
父亲的不在这放着
Daddy Dearest isn't here.
那在哪？
So where is he?
你大哥在里面到底干什么？
So, what is your brother doing in there?
查看死亡证明文件 看能不能找到以赛亚的尸体哪去了
Searching county death certificates.To learn what happened to lsaiah's body.
他是怎么混进去的？
How'd he even get in the door?
大概撒撒谎 打打花枪之类的
Lying and subterfuge, mostly.
你有一个…
You have a, um…
你脸上粘了一根睫毛…
You have an eyelash on your…
就在那
Your right-No. Uh, you know what?
- 你介意我 - 不介意
- Do you mind if i? - No.
那好
Okay.
好了
Okay, I got it.
许个愿吧
Make a wish.
- 萨姆 能问你点事情吗？- 当然
- Sam, can I ask you something? - Yeah, sure.
我并不是想那么仓促 你知道女孩子是可以等上很久的
I don't mean to be forward, but a girl could wait here forever.
我们之间是不是有什么火花 还是只是我自作多情而已？
Is there something here between us? Or am I delusional?
不是你在自作多情
You're not delusional.
可是接下来还有个转折对吧
But there's a "but" coming.
可是… 我不觉得这样是个好主意
But I don't think this would be a good idea.
我能问为什么吗？
Can I ask why?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
你把我搞糊涂了
Wait. You lost me.
这真的很难解释
Look, it's hard to explain.
只是我身边的人…
It's just that when people are around me…
总是会受到伤害
I don't know, they get hurt.
- 你什么意思？- 我是指身体上受到伤害
- What do you mean? - I mean, like, physically hurt.
只要关系到我和我大哥现在在做的事情实在是
With what my brother and I do, it's…
莎拉…
Sarah…
我曾经有个女朋友
l had a girlfriend.
后来她去世了 我母亲也去世了
And she died. And my mom died too.
我不知道 反正就象…
I don't know, it's like…
就象是我被诅咒了一样…
It's like l'm cursed or something.
就象死神总会出现在我身边
Like death just follows me around.
我自己并不是很怕 可是如果我对某个人有感觉的话
I'm not scared of much. But if I let myself have feelings for anybody-
你害怕她也会受到伤害对吧？
You're scared they'd get hurt too.
你这样想真的很贴心 也很古板 - 什么？
- That's very sweet. And very archaic. - Sorry?
我已经是个大人了 萨姆
Look. l'm a big girl, Sam.It's not your job…
我不需要你来为我做什么决定
to make decisions for me.
人总是随时随地都可能会受伤的
There's always a chance of getting hurt.
我不是指伤心或是意外这类的事
Heart and a tub of Hagen-Dazs.I'm not talking about a broken.
我是指那些关乎生命危险的事情
I'm talking life and death.
可明天我也可能被公车撞倒
Tomorrow I could get hit by a bus.
生命正是如此
That's what life is.
我知道失去挚爱的感觉很难过
Look. I know losing somebody you love, it's terrible.
你把自己封闭起来 相信我 我知道是什么感觉
You shut yourself off.Believe me, I know.
可当你把伤痛封闭起来的同时…
But when you shut out pain.
你也封住了其他人对你的关心
you shut out everything else too.
莎拉 你不明白 我所经历的那种伤痛…
Sarah, you don't understand.The pain that I went through…
我不能再承受一次了 真的不能
l can't go through it again. I can't.
我有打扰到你们吗？
Am I interrupting something?
- 没有 - 一点也没有
- No. - Not at all.
- 显而易见 - 你有查到什么？
- Huh. Apparently. - So, what did you get?
有所收获 看来默钱特一家剩下的亲戚
Pay dirt. The surviving relatives of the Merchant family…
都以以赛亚为耻 所以他们不想让他和家人同葬
were so ashamed of Isaiah, they didn't want him interred with the family.
所以他们把他的尸体交给郡里 郡里给了他穷人的葬礼
They handed him over to the county.County gave him a pauper's funeral.
那种经济型的 所以他并没有被火化
Economy style. Turns out he wasn't cremated.
只是被装进了廉价的棺材
he was buried in a pine box.
所以我们得去烧他的尸骨 - 是有尸骨去烧
- So there are bones to burn. - There are bones to burn.
告诉我你知道地方了
Tell me you know where.
你们看起来似乎 对这种事情出人意料的冷静
You guys seem to be uncomfortably comfortable with this.
这种挖坟墓的事情我们不是头一回了
Well, this isn't exactly the first grave we've dug.
还觉得我是结婚的好对象吗？
Still think l'm a catch?
挖到东西了
Think I got something.
你真是作恶多端啊 Isaiah
You've been a real pain in the ass, Isaiah.
安息吧
Good riddance.
迪恩 不要熄火
Keep the motor running.
我以为那幅画现在已经无害了
I thought the painting was harmless now.
为保险起见 最好还是连画一起搞定
Better safe than sorry We're gonna bury the sucker.
- 我想和你一起去 - 你确定吗？
- I wanna come with you.You sure? - Yeah.
嘿
- Hey. Hey, hey.
我就待车上 你进去要采取行动
I'll stay here, you go make your move.
萨姆 我说真的
Sam. l'm serious.
你是鬼怪方面的专家 萨姆…
Uh, Sam, you're the expert on all this ghost stuff.
这幅画应该是这样子的吗？
Is that paintingsupposed to look like that?
画中的小女孩哪去了？
Where's the little girl?
还有剃刀？
And the razor.
迪恩 嘿 是你吗？
Dean! Hey. ls that you?
萨姆 你没事吧？
Sammy, you all right?
- 告诉我是你关的门 - 不是我 我想是那个小女孩
- Tell me you slammed the door. - lt wasn't me. It was the girl.
女孩？什么女孩？
Girl? What girl?
- 她不在画中了 - 我猜整件事都是她在搞鬼
She's out of the painting.Might've been her all along.
父亲低头看的不是她吗？
Wasn't the dad looking at her?
- 也许他是在试着警告我们- 我们稍后再说 先想办法出来
- Maybe he was warning us. - Let's recap later, all right? Get us out.
我正在撬锁 不过好象没什么用
Trying to pick the lock.Door won't budge.
- 撞坏它 - 听着 天才 我去拿我的工具
- Then break it down. - Okay. Let me grab my battering ram.
- 迪恩 那鬼东西就要来了 - 我想出办法之前你要坚持住
- Dean, it's coming. - Hold it off…
找到什么盐和铁器之类的
until I figure something.Get salt or iron. Come on.
这什么鬼房子竟然没有盐？你有找到什么铁器吗？
What house doesn't have salt?Low-sodium freaks. Find any iron?
- 没有 要拿来干吗？- 铁器能驱除鬼魂
- No. What's it for? - lron repels evil.
可是必须是纯铁快点
But it's got to be pure. Hurry.
迪恩 再等会 别离开
Uh, Dean. Give me a sec.Don't go anywhere.
查看下椅子 有时候座位会…
Look in the chair.Sometimes the seats.
萨姆
Sam.
这么做是不对的
That is just so wrong.
铁器？
Iron?
对
Yeah.
- 萨姆 你没事吧？- 暂时没事
- Sammy, you okay? - Yeah. For now.
- 我们怎么消灭她？- 我不知道 她的尸骨已经被火化了
- How we gonna waste her? - I don't know. She was cremated.
- 没什么可以拿来烧的 - 那她怎么还可能出现？
- Nothing left to burn. - How's she still around?
一定还有什么东西
There must be something else.
萨姆 等等 之前我们在拍卖行里有出售古董娃娃
Sam, wait. We used to handle antique dolls at the auction.
那可真不错 莎拉 干嘛现在才说这个？
That's fascinating, Sarah, but important right now?
那时候 娃娃的样子是照着夭折的孩子的样子做的
Well, back then, they used to make the dolls in the kids' image.
我是说完全仿照 甚至会用上孩子的真头发
I mean, everything. Like they would use the kids' real hair.
迪恩 莎拉说那个娃娃可能植上了小女孩的头发？
Dean. Sarah says the doll might have the girl's hair.
遗体残留和尸骨一样
Human remains. Same as bones.
在那个墓冢
The mausoleum.
萨姆 快起来 快起来
Sam! Come on, push! Come on.
你真傻 迪恩
Come on, Dean.
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
萨姆 你没事吧？
Sam, you good?
没事
Not bad.
我在郡里的档案里发现了这个
This was archived in the county records.
默钱特家收养的女儿梅兰妮
The Merchant's adopted daughter, Melanie.
知道她为何被收养吗？
Know why she was up for adoption?
因为她自己的家人都在睡梦中被谋杀
Her real family was killed in their beds.
她杀了他们？
She killed them?
没错 可是谁会去怀疑她？一个天真无邪的小女孩
Who'd suspect her? Sweet little girl.
所以接下来她也杀死了以赛亚全家 所以父亲会很自责
So then she kills lsaiah and his family.The old man takes the blame.
他的灵魂从此也停留在画中 试着警告别人
His spirit's been trying to warn people ever since.
- 这件要搬哪去？- 搬到后面去烧毁
- Where's this one go? - Take it out back and burn it.
我是说真的 谢谢
I'm serious, guys. Thanks.
为什么那小女孩要做这种事？
So why'd the girl do it?
杀了别人 然后再自杀
Killing others? Killing herself?
有些人生来性格就扭曲 所以他们死后
Some people are just born tortured.So when they die…
- 灵魂也不会安息 - 可能就是那样 可是都不重要了
- …their spirits are just as dark. - Maybe. I don't care.
一切都结束了 已经都搞定了
It's over. We move on.
我猜这意味着你们要离开了
I guess this means you're leaving.
我在车里等你 再会 莎拉
I'll go wait in the car. See you, Sarah.
我才是那个烧毁了娃娃 消灭了恶鬼
I'm the one who burned the doll…
摧毁其精神的人 竟然谢都不谢我
and destroyed the spirit, but don't thank me or anything.
我有很多话想对你说
There are a million things that I want to say…
可是此时此刻 我竟然想不到怎么去表达
but for the life of me I can't think of one.
我也会想你的
Yeah, l'll miss you too.
- 你知道 至少这件事情上我们都学到了东西 - 什么？
- You know, there's a lesson in all of this. - What's that?
我们共同经历的这一切
We all got through this in one piece.
而我也没有受伤
I didn't get hurt.
没错 我很高兴你没事
Yeah, l'm glad for that.
所以也许不是你受诅咒了 也许吧…
So maybe you're not cursed. Maybe…
也许你有空可以回来看我
Maybe you'll come back and see me.
我会的
I will.
这才是我弟弟
That's my boy.